





206.353.7161



@browngirlbuilds

Drawing inspiration from my Graphic and Architectural Design background, I design experiences. I truly believe that every user is unique and my role is to create a clean, effective and well branded functional and visually pleasing experience.

SKILLS

Visual Design

Branding

Graphic Design

User experience design

User interface design

Project Management

Architectural Design

TOOLS

Adobe CS

HTML5 & CSS3

Wireframing

Sketch

EDUCATION

Startup Institute Chicago Web Design Track Summer 2015

SAIC Chicago Graphic Design Student Oct 2014-April 2015

University of Mumbai B.Arch in Architecture

•••••

EXPERIENCE:

Creative Director + Brand Strategist,

Gottesman Residential Real estate

Mar 2017 - present

Assist in building marketing and branding material both in print and for the web meeting all standards of the luxury real estate industry. Print ads include features in Luxe and other local publications.

Rebrand the look for the corporate, agent and property websites by building production-ready web pages for corporate website alongside founder and external development team, while balancing business requirements and technical proficiency. Adobe Creative Suite , HTML & CSS have been key in developing prototypes and presentation material.

Provide design suggestions to better enhance user experience; including legibility, accessibility and efficiency.

Creative Lead, Various Clients,

Brown Girl Builds

Aug 2015- present

Collaborate with startups, non-profits, local businesses, independent and business owners to lead design on branding, presentation decks, marketing materials, logo design and social media branding. Maintained flexibility in satisfying the client's needs and budget while maintaining the highest standards for visual and user-centered design.

User experience and Interface Designer,

BeerMapper

Jul 2015- Aug 2015

Responsible for supporting and promoting app design best practices throughout the product life-cycle in an Agile environment for BeerMapper. Starting with low-fidelity wireframes to high-fidelity prototypes and then working closely with product and sales teams to push to production.



INTERESTS

Food

Travel

Mosaic making Sustainable Design

Anything Marvel & Star Trek

OTHER EXPERIENCE:

Lead Designer,

Sarva Design - Seattle

Jul 2011- Jan 2014

Designed and managed various residential design projects in collaboration with clients and various vendors. Played a key role from the conception till completion of every project.

Architect and Project Manager

India

2003-2010

INFORMATION

nitya.28@gmail.com

- nitya-jain.github.io
- @browngirlbuilds
- 206.353.7161

REFERENCE:

Leah Petri

leah@gottesmanresidential.com 512-239-9964

Allie Fleming

allie@alliefleming.com 847-220-0960

Fernando Pohina

fpohina@gmail.com 425-766-5790

Vishal Sood

vishalsood114@gmail.com 206-434-8613